主持人:今晚,
Host: Tonight, some lucky contestant will walk out of here with fame,
某位走运的参赛选手将带着荣誉,财富和新闻界的至高无上的尊重离开赛场!!!
fortune, and the total respect of the journalism community!!!
普利策新闻奖颁奖的时间到了!
Yes, it's time for the Pulitzer Prize!!!
这里是我们的参赛选手,来自于,
And here are our contestants; from the "Washington Post",
Woodward和Bernstein!!!
Woodward and Bernstein!!!
观众:耶!!!
Crowd: Yeah!!!!
Host: From his retirement home in Martha's Vineyard
You know him, you love him, and boy do you trust him??!!Walter Cronkheit
观众:耶!!!
Crowd: Yeah!!!
观众:下面是,来自于的,麦琪*希佛!!!
Host: Then, from the "Long Island Daily Herald", Maggie Seaver!!!
麦琪:喔-----!!
Maggie: Woooo!!
观众:谁?
Crowd: Who?
观众:麦琪*希佛!!
Host: Maggie Seaver!!
观众:哈!哈!哈!
Crowd: Ha!Ha!Ha!
麦琪:杰森,怎么了?
Maggie: Jason, what's going on?
Jason: What were you thinking Maggie?I mean, Woodward and Bernstein, Walter Cronkheit!You're not
in their league.Ha!Be thankful you have a job!Ha ha
麦琪:杰森 ,你为什么像这样和我说话.
Maggie: Jason, why are you talking to me like this?
杰森:不要问我,麦琪.这是你的梦想.
Jason: Don't ask me Maggie.It's your dream.I mean look at this!
看!我会穿这个么?哈哈!
Would I wear polka dots?Ha Ha!!
(麦琪醒来)
(Maggie wakes up)
麦琪:杰森!杰森!杰森!
Maggie: Jason!Jason!Jason!
杰森:麦琪!这是什么?麦琪!!
Jason: Maggie!What is it?Maggie!!
麦琪:杰森?
Maggie: Jason?
杰森:在,杰森在这儿,亲爱的.
Jason: Yes,it's Jason,honey.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,
Maggie: Oh, honey, I just had the weirdest...the scariest dream!!
我刚才做了个很怪……非常可怕的梦!!我成了只小鸡,
I was a chicken,
and I was nominated for the Pulitzer Prize with Walter Cronkheit and Woodward
and Bernstein, but then everybody started laughing at me and making fun
对我打趣,我感觉坏极了!!!
and I felt terrible!!!
杰森:你成了只小鸡?
Jason: You were a chicken?
麦琪:甚至连你都对我很残酷.
Maggie: Even you were cruel to me.
杰森:亲爱的,我明白.我也有这样的……
Jason: Honey, I know what this is.I have this...
麦琪:难道你不打算道歉么?
Maggie: Won't you even apologize?
杰森:为什么?
Jason: For what?
麦琪:因为是那么的残酷!!
Maggie: For being so cruel!
杰森:亲爱的,那只是你的一个梦.
Jason: Honey, it was your dream.
麦琪:你在我梦里就是这么说的!即使在梦醒之后,
Maggie: That's exactly what you said in my dream!
我也不会买你帐的.
And I didn't buy it then either!!
杰森:对不起.
Jason: I'm sorry.
麦琪:这我好多了.
Maggie: That's better.
杰森:亲爱的,梦是你潜意识传达的信息,
Jason: Honey, dreams are just little messages from your subconscious.
你应该把它想作是被传达的一些电报.
You have to think of it as being sent little telegrams.
麦琪:那,这是什么样的信息?
Maggie: So, what's the message?
杰森:昨晚我们去了新闻界颁奖晚宴,
Jason: Well, alright.We went to the Journalism Awards Dinner last night,
你没有获奖.
and you didn't win anything.
麦琪:耶?
Maggie: Yeah?
杰森:所以,这些梦表明,你担心你不是个优秀的记者.
Jason: So, you're afraid that, well that means, you're not a good reporter.
麦琪:杰森!我怎么会担心自己是不是一个优秀的记者.
Maggie: Jason!I am certainly not afraid I am a good reporter.
杰森:我知道.
Jason: I know.
麦琪:我的意思是,我怎么会担心自己是不是个合格的记者.
Maggie: I mean, a bad reporter!
杰森:你是合格的记者.
Jason: Yes.
麦琪:如果我第二次连续落选任何奖项,
Maggie: And, it doesn't matter to me one little bit that I was over-looked
那对我来说没什么.
for the second year in a row.
杰森:是的,没什么.
Jason: No.
麦琪:我赢了个小小的长岛新闻奖,又能如何呢?呃?
Maggie: What do I need a silly little Long Island Journalism Award for?Huh?
杰森:嗯-------
Jason: Mmmm.
麦琪:提心我自己是不是个合格的记者!!
Maggie: Afraid I'm a bad reporter!!
杰森:嗯---
Jason: Mmm.
麦琪:那是个多么大的笑话?!
Maggie: What kind of a crack is that?
Jason: Mr.Whattney, I can't help you if you don't communicate
病人:如果我告诉你事实,
Patient: If I tell you things,
那我怎么确定你不会背过身去出嚼舌头……60分钟?
how do I know you won't turn around and sell it...to Sixty minutes?
杰森:病人-大夫间的关系是神圣的,我从未背弃过,
Jason: The patient-Doctor relationship is practically sacred.
我将来也不会背弃.
I've never violated it, and I never will.
病人:好,我把所有的都告诉你.
Patient: OK.I'll tell you everything.
杰森:对不起,您的时间到了.
Jason: Well, I'm sorry, your time's up.
病人:好!
Patient: Great!
杰森:Whattney先生,
Jason: You know, Mr.
这几周的某个时候,
Whattney, one of these weeks we're gonna have to get around to why you're
你一定要告诉我您来这儿就诊的原因.
here.
病人:对,好!好!好!下周,我保证.
Patient: Yeah right!Right!Right!Next week, I promise.
接听电话:(麦琪)嗨,亲爱的,是我.你看完病人,马上给我个电话.不用等,挂了电话,就听!还记得昨晚新闻颁奖宴会发言人的发言么?
Answer phone: (Maggie) Hi honey, it's me.Call me the second you're through with your
patient.No wait; put down the phone and listen!I said listen!Now, remember the
keynote speaker at the Journalism Awards banquet last night
杰森:Max Drummond.
Jason: Max Drummond.
接听电话:(麦琪)Max Drummond!对!!不管怎么说,
Answer phone: (Maggie) Max Drummond!That's right!!
很意外的,他打电话我,说他认为我很有才华,
Anyway, out of the blue,
并且具备了施展才能的机会.之后,
he calls me and says he thinks I'm talented and ready for the big time.
他给了我一个在他的报社工作的机会.我,要负责"纽约世界报"!!
Then he offers me a job on his paper.Jason!
难道不令人心驰神往么?喂,是不是啊?
Me, running for the "New York Clarion"!!Isn't that fantastic?Well isn't it?
杰森:对!
Jason: Yeah!
接听电话:我也是这么想的.最后,
Answer phone: I thought so too.
我告诉我需要些时间来仔细考虑,
Well when I could finally talk,
当然还要和你商量.然后,
I told him I needed some time to think it over,
他说他想请你我今晚和他夫妻二人共进晚餐.他说他希望能在社交场合认识我们.
and of course to talk to you.
难道这不让人高兴么?再见,
Then he said he wanted you and me to have dinner tonight with him and
亲爱的.
his wife.He said he'd like to get to know us socially.Isn't this exciting?
不要就傻坐在那么.给我打电话!
Bye, sweetheart.Well don't just sit there.Call me!
杰森:好了,麦琪!我们得八点钟之前到曼哈顿!
Jason: Come on Maggie!We gotta be in Manhattan by Eight!
麦琪:你在想什么?
Maggie: What do you think?
杰森:如果这人不想雇你,那我会的.
Jason: If this guy doesn't hire you, I will.
麦琪:哦,杰森,他为什么不会雇我?
Maggie: Oh Jason, why wouldn't he hire me?
杰森:我确信他……
Jason: Well, I'm sure he...
麦琪:可是,好了,告诉我,他会雇我的理由?
Maggie: But, then again, why would he hire me?
杰森:他应该知道……
Jason: He's gotta know that...
麦琪:也许,这个工作根本不存在.也许这只是场梦,跟其它梦没有什么不同!
Maggie: Maybe there isn't a job.Maybe this is all the same bad dream!
杰森:亲爱的,放松.
Jason: Honey, relax.If this were a dream,
如果这只是个梦,对我来说更好.
I'd be wearing more comfortable shoes.
麦琪:不,你说得对,
Maggie: No, you're right, I'm sorry.I'm just being a big chicken!
对不起.我太天真了.
That's why I was a chicken in my dream.
杰森:你会忘了那个梦么?你是个有才华的,
Jason: Will you forget that dream?You're a talented experienced reporter...
有经验的记者……只不过时运不济罢了.
who just happens to lay eggs.
麦琪:对.
Maggie: You're right.
杰森:不过,我希望不是.
Jason: I hope not.
麦琪:不必须得清楚自己在干什么,我的意思是说,
Maggie: I mean I must know what I'm doing.
一个纽约市的主编想雇我是不是还有什么其它原因?
I mean why else would a New York City editor want to hire me?
杰森:对.
Jason: Right.
麦琪:谢谢.
Maggie: Thank you.
杰森:时候到了,
Jason: It's about time you tuned into what everybody else already knows...
该你变成其它所有人.
and that is, how totally terrific you are.
迈克:爸爸,让那女人走!妈妈在楼上!等等.
Mike: Dad, get that woman out of here!Mom's upstairs!Wait a second.
那美女很辣,很性感,是不是,妈妈?
Is that hot, sexy babe, Mom?
麦琪:难道他不是很有趣么?
Maggie: Isn't he sweet?
杰森:还不只是这个.开萝尔!本!!我们走了!
Jason: Among other things.Carol!Ben!We're leaving!
迈克:好了.
Mike: Alright.
本:好运!
Ben: Good luck!
开萝尔:当心折了你的腿!
Carol: Break a leg!
迈克:好好玩.别担心,不用担心,我们会让开萝尔听话的.
Mike: Yeah, you guys have fun.And don't worry, we'll keep Carol in line.
麦琪:再见,孩子们.
Maggie: Bye bye guys.
迈克,开萝尔和本:再见!!好运.
Mike, Carol and Ben: Bye!!Good luck.
本:冰琪淋!!!
Ben: Ice cream!!!
开萝尔:我们会让开萝尔听话的?
Carol: We'll keep Carol in line?
迈克:对,来!我的意思是说,我们知道你是个什么样的麻烦制造者!!
Mike: Yeah, come on!I mean, we know what a nutty trouble maker you are!!
开萝尔:我?
Carol: Me?Who's the one who's always training up around here, huh?
经常在这儿被教训的是谁,啊?
Who's the one who's always telling you to get your smelly tennis shoes
经常训斥你把臭气冲天的鞋子从沙发上拿下去的是谁?
off the couch?
迈克:哦,啊,不要忘了还有一个呢,开萝尔.
Mike: Oh, ah, don't forget the other one Carol.
开萝尔:哦,我不会的.这儿,接着.
Carol: Oh, I won't.Here, catch.
(她用力一掷,打碎了一个花瓶.)
(She breaks a vase with her throw.)
本:我没有做过!!
Ben: I didn't do it!!
Waiter: Monsieur et Madame, Drummond should be along shortly.Bon Appetit
麦琪和杰森:谢谢.
Maggie and Jason: Thank you.
麦琪:哇.他们雇过在的时候,
Maggie: Wow.When they hired me at the "Herald" all they bought me was
他们买给我的所有东西就是鸡块.嗨,这就是我曾经梦想的……
Chicken McNuggets.Hey, that's what my dream was about...
杰森:麦琪!如果你爱我,你会忘记那个梦.嗨,
Jason: Maggie!If you love me, you'll forget that dream.Hey, relax sweetheart.
放松点,亲爱的.你现在工作地很优秀.
You're good at what you do.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,你说得对.知道么,我属于这儿.
Maggie: Oh honey, you're right.You know, I do belong here.
Drummond: Maggie, Maggie, Maggie.Oh, don't you look just lovely
麦琪:谢谢.这是我的丈夫……
Maggie: Thank you.This is my husband...
Drummond:杰森.
Drummond: Jason.
杰森:对.
Jason: Yeah.
Drummond:我们在长岛出版社见过面.
Drummond: We met at the Long Island Press Awards.
杰森:对.您的演讲很精彩.
Jason: Yes.I enjoyed your speech.
Drummond:那当然.请坐,请坐.
Drummond: Of course.Sit, sit, sit.
侍者:Drummond先生.
Waiter: Monsieur Drummond.
Drummond:抱歉.说话.
Drummond: Oh.Excuse me.Drummond!Talk!
Yeah, well tell the Senator, we're gonna go with the story that's written
I run this newspaper.Well, we can play hard ball too.Yeah
Drummond:我们也可以应付更加艰难的工作.抱歉,
Do you mind if I take a second just to clear my head?
Drummond:耽误一会我去整理一下.我保证,
Ah, well, I promise you,
Drummond:今晚不会再有公事打扰我们了.
that is the last business interruption for the evening.
Drummond:麦琪,你简直让我着迷.
Maggie, you have my undivided attention.
麦琪:杰森和我刚才正在说呢,这个餐馆好棒啊……
Maggie: Well, Jason and I were just saying what a lovely restaurant...
杰森:这是……
Jason: This is...
Drummond: Maggie, let me get right to the point.I want you!I need you
And I'm not gonna let you go till you say yes
麦琪:Max,你有点让人接受不了.
Maggie: Well, Max, you're overwhelming.
马格:对不起,鼻尖出汗了.
Margo: Sorry, shiny nose.
Drummond: This is my lovely wife, Margo.This is Maggie, and Jason Seaver
马格:哦,我的天呀.
Margo: Oh, my goodness.
Drummond:你们认识?
Drummond: You two know each other?
马格:难道杰森长得不像我的兄弟贝尔么?
Margo: Well, doesn't Jason look exactly like my brother, Bill?
Drummond:你的兄弟长的像B.Arthur.
Drummond: Your brother looks like B.Arthur.
杰森:很多人长得像B. Arthur.
Jason: A lot of guys look like B.Arthur.
Drummond:噢,该说的都说了,
Drummond: Well, now that we got that all straightened out,
why don't we just sit down and relax, and enjoy the rest of the evening
Drummond:麦琪,你决定了吗?
Maggie, do you have that answer for me yet?
麦琪:我在想.我跳舞的时候思考地更好.
Maggie: I'm thinking.I think better when I dance.
杰森:耶……
Jason: Ye...
Drummond:我也这么认为.
Drummond: Me too!
麦琪:哦,好吧.
Maggie: Oh, OK.
马格:世界真小,啊,医生?
Margo: Small world, huh, Doctor?
杰森:非常小.
Jason: Very.
马格:在我们的会议上,我用的是我结婚前的名字,
Margo: I use my maiden name in our sessions, cos Max is kind o' famous.
Max would have a fit if he knew I told anybody, he's the sleaziest
他是个脚踏两只船,追逐女人的坏男人.
two-timing, skirt-chaser he is.
杰森:我自己可能得生会儿气.
Jason: Well, I may have a fit myself.
马格:哦,上帝!我想,
Margo: Oh God!I just realized, everything I told you,
我告诉你的一切,你可以告诉你的妻子,而且她可以告诉……
you could tell your wife, and she could tell...
杰森:不,不,任何人我都不会告诉.你我之间,
Jason: No, no, I can't tell anybody.
是病人与医生的关系,两人之间的东西,是严格保密的.
What goes on between you and I, patient to doctor, is strictly confidential.
马格:好.不,
Margo: Good.No, bad.
这太糟了.
If your wife actually believes that my husband wants to hire her for her
如果你的妻子真的以为我丈夫想雇她是因为她的才华,那她已经上钩了.
talent, he's got her hooked.
侍者:您想要听当今的流行歌曲么?
Waiter: Would you like to hear the catch of the day?
杰森(在自己心里):我认为我跟她结婚了.
Jason (in his mind): I think I'm married to her.
迈克:本,这个就是妈妈的崭新的灯么?
Mike: Say Ben, wasn't this Mom's brand-new lamp?
本:我很高兴刚才我在厨房里,她当时差点把它打碎.
Ben: I'm just glad I was in the kitchen when Carol tried trashed it.
开萝尔:你们能不能闭嘴.
Carol: Would you guys shut up.
迈克:你会以为开萝尔会知道如何使用那胶水.
Mike: You know, you'd figure Carol would know how to use something called "
Goofy Glue."
本:我觉得她需要的是书虫胶水!
Ben: I think she needs some Nerd Glue!
迈克:得了,本!
Mike: Alright Ben!
本:来!
Ben: Come on!
开萝尔:好,好,这么办,你们俩得帮我把这个重新粘好.我会把它放成另一种模样,爸爸和妈妈回到家,看到这灯坏了,你们觉得他们会相信是谁打碎的?
Carol: OK, OK, here's the deal; you two are gonna help me glue this back together again.I'll put it another way; when Mom and Dad come home and see this broken lamp, who do you think they'll believe did it?
迈克:哦,好,都怪本.
Mike: Oh, sure, fine, blame little Ben.
本:嗨!
Ben: Hey!
开萝尔:无论什么时候本有麻烦,他们经常说的坏榜样是谁?
Carol: And whenever Ben gets in trouble, who do they always say is the bad example?
迈克:嗨!你不会对爸爸妈妈撒谎吧,是不是?
Mike: Hey!Come on, you wouldn't lie to 'em would you?
开萝尔:哦,我会的,而且,我会很喜欢那么做的.
Carol: Oh, I would, and I'd enjoy it.
迈克:为了我们的小妹妹,干什么都可以.
Mike: Anything for our little sis.
麦琪:不,还不是.Max,是什么让您觉得我已经具备条件可以胜任的工作呢?
Drummond: Was that a "yes" I heard?
Drummond:从你写的文章中就可以看出来.
Maggie: No, not yet anyway.
Max, what makes you think I'm ready for the New York Clarion?
麦琪:那我的文章都告诉了你什么?
Drummond: Well, I can tell from your writing.
麦琪:哦,我……也差不太多.
Maggie: And what does my writing tell you?
Drummond: Oh, your writing tells me, that you're very talented, mature
Drummond:自信,
fairly self confident, with absolutely no doubts about who you are or
Drummond:你对自己是谁能做什么事从未怀疑过,对吗?
where you're headed; am I right?
麦琪:噢,……可能吧.
Maggie: Oh, I'm...Pretty close.
马格:这事够了么,足以让你恶心,是不是?
Margo: Is that enough to make you puke, or what?Oh, he's subtle, very subtle.
哦,他会慢慢来,非常慢地周旋.
Right about now, he's telling her how much he admires her work and how
现在,他在告诉她他有多么的赞赏她的工作,她的工作多么地反映她的为人.
much that reflects on her as a person.
杰森:我的妻子是个非常聪明的女人.
Jason: My wife is a very smart woman.
马格:哦,对不起.
Margo: Oh I'm sorry.
杰森:我们不应该哪怕是讨论这件事.这对我来说非常的窘迫.
Jason: You know, we shouldn't even be discussing this.This is very awkward for me.
马格:不,你是对的,你是对的.
Margo: No, you're right, you're right.
哦,我肯定你的妻子比那还要镇静自若.我的意思是说,
Oh, I'm sure your wife is much more together than that.
她被雇一周后,他会向她摊牌,
I mean, a week after she's hired, he'll hit on her, she'll turn him down,
她会拒绝他,而他会解雇她.这样肯定会让你觉得好一些.
and he'll give her the axe.I bet that makes you feel a lot better.
杰森:哦,会好许多.
Jason: Oh, much.
马格:也许我应该敦促你有些变化.
Margo: Maybe I should charge you for a change.
我先去一下洗手间,
I think I'll go to the powder room;
这个东西我一次只能用一点.
I can only take a little of this at a time.
杰森(在自己心里):我不能提醒麦琪,我什么事也不能说.
Jason (in his mind): And, I can't warn Maggie.I can't say anything.
迈克:哦,太好了.
Mike: Oh, perfect.
开萝尔:挺好啊.你们觉得有道理么?
Carol: It isn't bad.Do you think it'll hold?
迈克:什么!你在开玩笑?
Mike: What!Are you kidding?
在广告上,这东西能拉东西五头大象穿过大峡谷.
On the commercial this stuff holds five elephants over the Grand Canyon.
本:对,在电视上放的没有不真实的.
Ben: Yeah, and they don't put anything on TV that isn't true.
开萝尔:那好,我们非常明白了,你们俩收拾残局.
Carol: Well, we're in the clear now.You two clean up the mess.
迈克:哈.开萝尔,
Mike: Ha.Carol, if I'd clean up the mess round here,
如果收拾这儿的残局,可能也会把你给清理掉.
you'd probably find yourself standing in a trash can out by the curb.
开萝尔:来,本,起来.
Carol: Come on Ben, get up.
本:我不行,我陷住了!
Ben: I can't.I'm stuck!
迈克:你在开玩笑,是么?
Mike: You're kidding, right?
开萝尔:不,他没有.
Carol: No, he isn't!
本:啊-----!
Ben: Arrgghh!
迈克:你在叫什么呢?
Mike: What are you screaming about?
本:我不知道,以前我从来没有粘到一个桌子上过!
Ben: I don't know, I've never been glued to a table before!
迈克:哦,上帝.举着双手抱着我的脖子,我拉你的时候,我会猛地拉你.
Mike: Oh my God.Alright, put your hands round my neck, and when I pull
on you, I'll throw your weight towards me, OK
本:好.
Ben: OK.
迈克:准备好了?一,二,三!啊!哦,不!不!不!现在做什么?
Mike: Ready?One!Two!Three!Ahh!Oh no!No!No!What are we gonna do now?
Drummond: Did I tell you the number of Pulitzer Prize winning writers
on the Clarion?
麦琪:哦,没.
Maggie: Oh, no.
Drummond: Well, you'll have to wait till I have a chat with the chef
Drummond:我准备了一份丰盛的晚餐.
I have a very special dinner planned.
杰森(在自己的心里):对,拿麦琪当甜点.
Jason (in his mind): Yeah, with Maggie as dessert.
麦琪:哦,杰森,这真是最迷人的一夜,难道我还在做梦么?
Maggie: Oh Jason, is this the most fantastic night, or am I dreaming?
杰森:就这两种选择么?
Jason: Are these the only two choices?
麦琪:你不会想信的Max有多么需要我.
Maggie: You cannot believe how much Max wants me.
杰森:哦,不,我能.
Jason: Oh, yes I can.
麦琪:他说他有个非常有好的职位给我,而我呢不用像在那样写些小故事.我最终有幸第一次做真正的新闻……犯罪……腐败……
Maggie: He says he has a very exciting position in line for me.
And I wouldn't be doing cute little stories like they do at the Herald.
I'd finally for the first time get to do hard news...real news...crime...
corruption...
杰森:谋杀?
Jason: Murder?
麦琪:如果我幸运的话.
Maggie: If I'm lucky.
杰森(在自己的心里):麦琪,我怎么不明说就能让你明白呢?
Jason (in his mind): Maggie, how can I tell you, without telling you?
麦琪:你是怎么想的?
Maggie: Well, what do you think?
杰森:亲爱的,你应该再考虑考虑.
Jason: Well, honey, I think, you should think.
麦琪:就这样?我能从算命书中得到更好的建议.
Maggie: That's it?I'd get better advice from a Fortune Cookie.
杰森:我觉得你已经……已经仔细地衡量了所有的可能性了么?
Jason: Well, I mean, I think that you've...err...
You've got to carefully weigh all of the possibilities here.
麦琪:我正在努力.你觉得我应该怎么做?
Maggie: Well, I'm trying.What do you think I should do?
杰森:我觉得……有不同的角度.考虑一下.
Jason: I think th...the...there are angles.Think.
麦琪:可是,我应该接受这份工作么?
Maggie: But should I take the job?
杰森(在自己的心里):看着我的眼睛,这儿.
Jason (in his mind): Look at my eyes, it's right there.
杰森:你不应该今晚就做决定.
Jason: I don't think you should make that decision tonight.
麦琪:杰森,发生了什么事?
Maggie: Jason, what's going on?
你听起来突然像是你在白宫上班似的?
You suddenly sound like you work in the White House.
杰森:麦琪,我能给你的唯一帮助是告诉你问一下自己,
Jason: Maggie, the only help I can give you is to tell you to ask yourself,
为什么你真的想要这份工作?以及,为什么Max需要你?
why you really want the job, and why Max wants you.
杰森(在自己的心里):我真的听起来像是在白宫工作.
Jason (in his mind): I do sound like I work in the White House.
本:我觉得好多了.
Ben: I feel much better.
开萝尔:妈妈爸爸回家的时候你就不会了.
Carol: You won't when Mom and Dad get home.
迈克:站一边!重大的问题需要重大的解决方案.
Mike: Stand aside!Big problems call for big solutions!
开萝尔:具体是什么?
Carol: What is that?
迈克:就是对我们祈祷的回答,电动打磨机.
Mike: It's the answer to our prayers; the electric sander.
本和开萝尔:晚上好!
Ben and Carol: Goodnight!
迈克:好了!你们要去哪儿?
Mike: Come on!Where are you guys going?
开萝尔:哪儿都行,除了这儿之外.
Carol: Anywhere but here.
迈克:哦,好了,兄弟们,
Mike: Oh, come on guys, relax, relax!Now this is a fool-proof plan, right?
放松,放松!这是个傻子证明计划,
Now, all we gotta do is we glide the sander over the table top a couple
不是么?我们需要做的只是用打磨机轻轻过滑过桌子的表面,使之完全吻合,上漆,
of swoops.We sand it to a perfect match, it dries by morning,
早上就会干.我们会在隐蔽的地方干.你们觉得怎么样?
and we got it made in the shade.So what do you guys think?
本和开萝尔:迈克!迈克!迈克!
Ben and Carol: Mike!Mike!Mike!
迈克:要么这样,要么我们告诉妈妈爸爸说,是我们弄坏了咖啡桌.你想不想那么干,
Mike: Guys.Guys.It's either this or we tell Mom and Dad that we ruined
本?开萝尔?好,我们都同意.
the coffee table.Now do you want to do that, Ben?Carol?Good, we agree.
不用担心,本.当你真正成为男人的那天,你会重新思考这件事情的.
Don't worry Ben; someday you'll look back on this as the day you became a man.
你也一样,开萝尔.关掉!关掉!
You too, Carol.Turn it off!!Turn it off!
开萝尔:拔掉!灯!!灯!!
Carol: Unplug it!!The lamp!!The lamp!!
Drummond:麦琪,我希望沉默表示你在思考.
Drummond: Err, Maggie, I hope your silence means you're thinking.
杰森(在自己心里):我真心希望如此.
Jason (in his mind): I sure hope so.
麦琪:哦,对.
Maggie: Oh, yes.
Drummond:希望是个好消息.
Drummond: Good thoughts, I hope.
麦琪:我做这个决定不应该有任何困难,我的意思是说,毕竟,
Maggie: You know, I shouldn't have any problem making this decision.I mean, after all,
我写过一篇关于职业选择的专栏.
wrote an entire feature article on career choices.
Drummond: Well, it wasn't really your feature writing that caught my eye
马格:抱歉.
Margo: Ha!Sorry, gas.
麦琪:那,会是什么?
Maggie: Well, what was it then?
Drummond: 事实报道.
Drummond: It was your hard news.
麦琪:事实报道,哦?
Maggie: Hard news, oh?
杰森(在自己的心里):什么样的事实报道?
Jason (in his mind): What hard news?
麦琪:比如我的城市犯罪系列?
Maggie: Like my urban crime series?
Drummond:是的.
Drummond: Exactly.
麦琪:关于政府腐败的的文章.
Maggie: My piece on government corruption.
杰森(在自己的心里):关于政府腐败的哪篇文章?
Jason (in his mind): What piece on government corruption?
Drummond:很好.
Drummond: Best.
麦琪:那篇谋杀审判.
Maggie: That vigilante murder trial.
杰森(在自己的心里):哦……
Jason (in his mind): Oh...real him in Maggie.
Drummond: I like what you wrote, better than what we printed
麦琪:不过,Max,
Maggie: Well Max, this really, really helps me make up my mind.
这真的让我最终下了决心.我得说,不.
I'm going to have to say, no.
Drummond:嘿,你把香槟酒溅到杰森身上了.
Drummond: Hey!Hey, you just spilt champagne all over Jason here.
杰森:我已经习惯了,我是个精神病科大夫.
Jason: I'm used to it, I'm a psychiatrist.
杰森(在自己的心里):你这傻瓜.
Jason (in his mind): You slime bucket.
麦琪:您的邀请真的让我受宠若惊,但我得说不行.
Maggie: I was truly flattered by your offer Max, but no.
Drummond: Well...err...Maggie, this is very important, you should really be
麦琪:我确定.
Maggie: I'm sure.
杰森(在自己心里):不不不不不不不.
Jason (in his mind): Na na na na na na.
麦琪:谢谢你,但是不.
Maggie: Thank you, but no thank you.
侍者(在自己心里):不不不不不不
Waiter (in his mind): Na na na na na na.
Waiter: Monsieur Drummond, dinner is served.I trust everything will be to your complete satisfaction
马格:今晚不是.
Margo: Not tonight.
杰森:不过,我饿了!你晚饭都点了些什么?这是什么?
Jason: Well, I am starved!What have you got here?What is it?
麦琪:晚上好,Max,
Maggie: Good night Max, Margo, thank you for a lovely, lovely evening.
马格.
He's got some nerve lying to me about how good my stories were,
他对我撒了一些大胆的谎,说我的故事有多么的好.
when I was lying to him about writing them.
杰森:亲爱的,对不起……真的.
Jason: Honey, I am sorry...really.
麦琪:我真的是对这份工作动心.有那么一阵子,我真的觉得我自己很优秀.
Maggie: And I was really excited about this job.I mean, for a while there
I actually thought I was good
杰森:你确实很优秀.
Jason: Well, you are.
麦琪:杰森,他之所以给我这个工作,
Maggie: Jason, he made this job offer because...
因为……因为他想跟我上床.
because he wanted to sleep with me.
杰森(在自己心里):哦,我得小心点说话了.
Jason (in his mind): Oh, I have to say something very clever here.
杰森:我真不敢想信!
Jason: I can't believe that!
麦琪:我能想像出来的合理的理由就是这个.他撒谎,他的褒扬,
Maggie: Well, that's the only thing that makes sense to me; his lies,
他和我跳舞的方式,他对妻子视而不见的模样,等等.
his compliments, the way he danced with me, the way he ignored his wife.
杰森:太让人震惊了!
Jason: Well, that's shocking!
麦琪:是么?等,
Maggie: Yeah?Well, wait till you hear this;
从他妻子的表情看来……她是知道的.
from the look on his wife's face...she knows.
杰森:这么看这件事,你留意到了所有的蛛丝马迹,
Jason: Well, look at it this way, you took all those clues,
把它们综合起来,
you put them all together, and you came up with the truth about Max Drummond,
得到了关于Max的真相.这就是一位优秀的记者所应具备的.
now that takes a very good reporter.
麦琪:我确实是那样子,不是么?
Maggie: I did do that, didn't I?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yes, you did.It's a feather in your cap.
麦琪:哦!羽毛!也许就是因为这个所以我的梦里才会出现小鸡.
Maggie: Oh!Feather!Maybe that's why there was a chicken in my dream.
杰森:闭上你的嘴!
Jason: Shut your beak!!
迈克:在我们所有的选择方案中,我们有足够的钱买个新的咖啡桌.好了,妈妈爸爸周六都睡得晚,因此明天我和本的第一件事就是去商店里买一张.
Mike: OK, now between all of our allowances, we've got enough money for a new coffee table.OK, and Mom and Dad sleep late on Saturdays, so first thing tomorrow
me and Benny will go down to Chadwick's and pick one up
本:他们回家了!他们走过来了!
Ben: They're home!They're here!They're coming!
开萝尔:快,他们回家了!
Carol: Quick, they're home!
迈克:好,本!本!坐下.现在,不要动,明白?
Mike: OK, Ben!Ben!Sit down!OK, now just don't move, OK?
本,迈克和开萝尔:嗨!
Ben, Mike and Carol: Hi!
麦琪:嗨.
Maggie: Hi.
杰森:嗨,大家好!一切都还好么?
Jason: Hi everyone!How is everything?
迈克:一切都很好,爸爸.
Mike: Everything's great Dad.
麦琪:本.
Maggie: Ben.
本:我也很好.
Ben: I'm great too.
麦琪:五分钟后上床睡觉.
Maggie: I want you in bed in five minutes.
本:好的.
Ben: OK.
杰森:迈克,你不要出去了,明白?
Jason: Mike, you'll lock up, OK?
迈克:是,那还用得着说么,爸爸.
Mike: Yeah, sure thing Dad.
杰森:好了,明天见.
Jason: Alright, we'll see you guys in the morning.
本,迈克和开萝尔:好了,晚安!
Ben, Mike and Carol: Alright, Good night!
杰森:晚安.
Jason: Good night.
本:哦,不!!啊----!!
迈克:那……你们俩晚餐吃的是什么?
00:23:04,700
Ben: Oh no!!Arrgghh!!! Mike: So...err...what did you guys have for dinner?